Finding aid for Harvey S. Day papers
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan,
Harvey S. Day Papers 1831-1935
Day, Harvey S.
1 linear ft.
851074 Aa 2
Dairy farmer in Willis, Michigan; personal and family correspondence and farm account books.
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
The collection (Donor No. 407 ) was donated by Walter S. Fry of Detroit in 1938.
The collection is open for research.
Harvey S. Day was a dairy farmer of Willis, Michigan and an officer of the Holstein-Friesian Association.
Personal and family correspondence, including letter, 1865, of Matthew Day written from Joe Holt Hospital; letters, 1892-1935, concerning Holstein-Friesian cattle and the activities of the Holstein-Friesian Association, and Day's dairy farm; also bills, receipts, cattle transfer certificates, records of milk poundage, account books, poetry, recipe book, and other miscellaneous papers.
Form and Genre:
Account books.; Poetry.
Subjects:
Day, Harvey S.; Holstein-Friesian Association of America.; Agriculture--Michigan--Washtenaw County.; Cookery.; Dairying--Michigan--Washtenaw County.; Farmers--Michigan--Washtenaw County.; Ypsilanti (Mich.)
Contributors:
Day, Matthew.
- Harvey S. Day Papers, 1831-1935
  - Correspondence
    - 1842-1865 (Box 1)
    - 1866-1870 (Box 1)
    - January-July 1871 (Box 1)
    - August-December 1871 (Box 1)
    - January-August 1872 (Box 1)
    - September 1872-1874 (Box 1)
    - 1875-1891 (Box 1)
    - 1892-1897 (Box 1)
    - 1898-1902 (Box 1)
    - 1903-1905 (Box 1)
    - 1906-1907 (Box 1)
    - 1908 (Box 1)
    - 1909 (Box 1)
    - January-September 29, 1910 (Box 1)
    - September 30-December 1910 (Box 1)
    - January-March 1911 (Box 1)
    - Undated (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous cards, notes, etc. (Box 1)
  - Holstein records, 6 folders (Box 1)
  - Printed poems (Box 1)
  - Manuscript poems (Box 1)
  - Day papers, (Removed from Simons and Seamans account book) (Box 1)
  - Records and statements
    - 1885-1892 (Box 1)
    - 1893-1895 (Box 1)
    - 1896-1898 (Box 1)
    - 1899-1901 (Box 1)
    - 1902-1908and undated (Box 1)
  - Clippings, 8 folders (Box 1)
  - Account book, ca. 1901-ca. 1902 (Box 1)
  - Account book, poems, recipes, ca. 1831-ca. 1859 (Box 1)
  - Milking accounts book, undated (Box 1)
  - Recipe book, undated (Box 1)